A Guide to Arena Stage Financial Documents and Projects, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University Libraries
A Guide to Arena Stage Financial Documents and Projects 1950-2000 1950-2000
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University Libraries
Arena 0012
27 containers comprising 13.2 cubic feet (19.8 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Dontaed to George Mason University Libraries in the fall of 2000.
Biographical/Historical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craft persons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content
Contains financial documents produced by Arena Stage between 1950-2000. Includes documents pertaining to budgets, marketing, royalties, grants, and donation information.
Arrangement
By subject
Contents List
- Arena Stage Financial Documents and Projects
  - Arena Stage Associates - Year End Stats 1982-1983 (Box Box 1)
  - Direct Mail fund raising/marketing stats, 1984-1985 (Box Box 1)
  - donor project / renewal letters 1989 (Box Box 1)
    planning information for gaining new donors
  - NEA challenge Grant III 1988 (Box Box 1)
  - 40th anniversary Budget, 1990 (Box Box 1)
  - 40th anniversary budget / 25th anniversary budget for the Living Stage (Box Box 1)
  - Zelda's 40th Anniversary fund (Box Box 1)
  - 40th anniversary gala table sales (Box Box 1)
  - 40th anniversary gala prospectus (Box Box 1)
  - 40th anniversary photo retrospective (Box Box 1)
    planning materials for retrospective
  - planned giving, 1990 (Box Box 1)
  - Development Report: Budget 1988-1989 (Box Box 2)
  - financial statements; 1985-1987 (Box Box 2)
  - 40th anniversary general information (Box Box 2)
  - 1988 focus group report: subscriptions and multi-ticket buyers (Box Box 2)
  - marketing and ticket buying survey: 1985 (Box Box 2)
  - management meeting minutes: 1989-1990 (Box Box 2)
  - Arena Stage Associates: year end stats 1978-1982 (Box Box 2)
  - preliminary proposal for annual fund 1985 (Box Box 2)
  - development calender, FY 1991 (Box Box 1)
  - communications 1990-1991 (Box Box 2)
  - Development Research Associate Computer Manual by Josh Milton (Box Box 2)
  - donor development research and stats mid 80's (Box Box 3)
  - Black History Month at the Arena Stage (Box Box 3)
  - misc. financial forms (Box Box 3)
  - draft "Underwriters' Support" article (Box Box 3)
  - Arena Stage graphics and logo (Box Box 3)
  - misc. charts, lists and financial reference information (Box Box 3)
  - sample thank you letters for donors (Box Box 3)
  - computer program information, notes (Box Box 3)
  - telemarketing information 1987-1988 season (Box Box 3)
  - phone/mail program report (Box Box 3)
  - telemarketing and mail marketing information (Box Box 3)
  - promo code report 1986-1987 (Box Box 3)
  - Institutional Development Counsel proposals (Box Box 3)
  - advertising spreadsheet (Box Box 3)
  - Saturn / Columbia Books vouchers (Box Box 3)
  - Asa and LS donor stats (Box Box 3)
  - campaign matrix information (Box Box 3)
  - fellows program information (Box Box 4)
  - London Tour 1988 - finances, contracts (Box Box 4)
  - London Tour 1988 - Correspondence/Press (Box Box 4)
  - London Tour - Final Deposits (Box Box 4)
  - London Arts Discovery tour information (Box Box 4)
  - London Tour 1989 (Box Box 4)
  - National VIP ticket hotline information (Box Box 4)
  - LS Outreach Project 1988 (Box Box 4)
  - advertising budget plans, 1981-1982 (Box Box 5)
  - subscription budget calender, 1981 (Box Box 5)
  - PR and Marketing budget info. 1981-1982 (Box Box 5)
  - subscription campaign 1982-1983 (Box Box 5)
  - subscription newsletter (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983, mailings and schedules (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983: renewal invoice (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983, brochure copy (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982: brochure copy (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982 renewal forms (Box Box 5)
  - subscription 1982-1983, minor printed materials (Box Box 5)
  - subscriptions 1982-1983 (Box Box 5)
  - subscription phone sales, 1982 (Box Box 6)
  - subscriptions 1982, printing bids (Box Box 6)
  - subscription 1982, print ads (Box Box 6)
  - subscription calender 1982 (Box Box 6)
  - "Washingtonian" subscription 1982-1983 (Box Box 6)
  - prospectus: Office for Advanced Drama Research (Box Box 6)
  - bicentennial celebrations, 1976 (Box Box 6)
  - bicentennial celebrations general (you can figure the date out on your own) (Box Box 6)
  - World Theater Festival, general info (Box Box 6)
  - World Theater Festival general (Box Box 6)
  - (Box Box 6)
  - Boston University Theater Renovation (Box Box 6)
  - 1967-1968 royalty information (Box Box 7)
  - "The Foursome" Royalty payments (Box Box 7)
  - payment to Bread and Puppet theater for performance (Box Box 7)
  - "Conflict of Interest" royalty payment (Box Box 7)
  - Royalties 1974-1975 season (Box Box 7)
  - Royalties 1975-1976 season (Box Box 7)
  - Workshop production royalties (Box Box 7)
  - Royalties 1976-1977 season (Box Box 7)
  - Royalties 1977-1978 season (Box Box 7)
  - "Nightclub Cantana" royalty payments (Box Box 7)
  - "Emigres" royalty payment (Box Box 7)
  - Royalties 1978-1979 season (Box Box 7)
  - Victor Borge, royalty payments (Box Box 7)
  - "Tiebele" royalty payments (Box Box 7)
  - royalty payment information, The Billy Bishop Company (Box Box 8)
  - "Loose Ends" royalty information (Box Box 8)
  - "Mummenschanz", royalty information (Box Box 8)
  - royalty information 1979-1980 (Box Box 8)
  - royalty information 1980-1981 (Box Box 8)
  - "Karamazov" production costs (Box Box 9)
  - "Karamozov" box office reports (Box Box 9)
  - "Banjo Dancing" production costs (Box Box 9)
  - "American Buffalo" cost sheets (Box Box 9)
  - "Rosewater Extension" cost sheets (Box Box 9)
  - "One Mo' Time" cost sheets and information (Box Box 9)
  - "Gertrude Stein" cost sheets (Box Box 9)
  - "Gertrude Stein", production costs (Box Box 9)
  - "K2", production extension costs (Box Box 9)
  - "Karamazov", production information (Box Box 9)
  - "Avner the Eccentric", production information (Box Box 9)
  - "Tomfoolery", extension of performance info (Box Box 9)
  - royalty information ,1981-1982 season (Box Box 9)
  - "Banjo Dancing" production information/costs (Box Box 9)
  - "Animal Cracker" production extension information (Box Box 9)
  - royalty information, 1982-1983 season (Box Box 9)
  - "Banjo" production information (Box Box 9)
  - royalty information, 1983-1984 (Box Box 9)
  - "Karamozov" cost information 1982-1983 (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo dancing" cost information 1982-1983 (Box Box 10)
  - Royalty information, 1982-1983 season (Box Box 10)
  - royalty information, 1984-1985 season (Box Box 10)
  - "Foolsfire" royalty info (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing" payments 1984-1985 (Box Box 10)
  - "Raisin" royalty income 1972-1973 (Box Box 10)
  - "Tintypes" Royalty income 1978-1979 (Box Box 10)
  - "Tintypes" royalty information 1978-1979 (Box Box 10)
  - "One Mo' Time" royalty income 1980-1981 (Box Box 10)
  - "Tom Foolery" royalty income 1981-1982 (Box Box 10)
  - "K2" NYC royalty info 1981-1982 (Box Box 10)
  - "Anarchist" royalty income 1983-1984 (Box Box 10)
  - "Execution" royalty income 1984-1985 (Box Box 10)
  - "Ourselves Alone" royalty income 1986-1987 (Box Box 10)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1977-1978 (Box Box 11)
  - Cafritz Foundation Grant 1975-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - Cafritz Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Cafritz Foundation 1977-1978 (Box Box 11)
  - Meyer Foundation 1975-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - Meyer Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Shubert Foundation Fiscal Report 1975 - 1976 (Box Box 11)
  - United Arts Fund 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box Box 11)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation grant, 1975-1978 (Box Box 11)
  - Barbara Henderson will - $5,000 (Box Box 11)
  - 1975-1976 fund drive - Changes Explanation (Box Box 11)
  - CBS Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Grant request - Queene Ferry Coonley Foundation 1975-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - Bender Foundation 1975-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - U.S. Steel Foundation 1972-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - Philip L. Graham Fund Bicentennial Grant, 1975-1976 (Box Box 11)
  - American Security and Trust Company $250,000 loan (Box Box 11)
  - Misc. Grants 1973-1979 (Box Box 12)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts (Box Box 12)
  - Case history of the economic workings of Arena Stage (Box Box 12)
  - Ford Foundation New Play Program (Box Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts - general (Box Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts 1946-1980 (Box Box 13)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978-1980 (Box Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation grants, 1962-1970 (Box Box 14)
  - NEA Challenge Grants 1977-1981 (Box Box 14)
  - Living Stage Grants 1976-1979 (Box Box 14)
  - The Albacus Group (Box Box 15)
  - Abbott Laboratories contributions (Box Box 15)
  - Abell Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Adams National Bank (Box Box 15)
  - Aetna Life and Casualty (Box Box 15)
  - AKC fund (Box Box 15)
  - ALCOA Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Alexander and Alexander gift (Box Box 15)
  - Alleco, Inc. Press info (Box Box 15)
  - Alleco, Inc. correspondence (Box Box 15)
  - Amax Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Amax, Inc. correspondence (Box Box 15)
  - American Broadcasting Co. (Box Box 15)
  - American International Group (Box Box 15)
  - American Road and Transportation Builders (Box Box 15)
  - American Satellite (Box Box 15)
  - AMOCO Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - AMP Incorporated (Box Box 15)
  - Anheuser-Busch Companies, Inc. (Box Box 15)
  - Annenberg Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Anson Mills Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - ARCA Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - The Arcadia Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - ARMCO Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - The Arthur Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Arundel Asphalt Products, Inc. (Box Box 15)
  - ASARCO Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Vincent Astor Foundation (Box Box 15)
  - Bank of Delaware (Box Box 15)
  - Barnes, Morris and Pardoe, Inc. (Box Box 15)
  - T.A. Beach Inc. (Box Box 15)
  - Bill Laboratories (Box Box 16)
  - W. Bell and Co., Inc. (Box Box 16)
  - Berger and Berman Builders, Inc. (Box Box 16)
  - Bernstein Family Foundation (Box Box 16)
  - Bethlehem Steel Corp. (Box Box 16)
  - B.F. Saul Real Estate Investments Trust (Box Box 16)
  - Black and Decker (Box Box 16)
  - BET Forum (Box Box 16)
  - Black Student Fund (Box Box 16)
  - Black Women's Community Foundation (Box Box 16)
  - Black Construction Company (Box Box 16)
  - The Bodman Foundation (Box Box 16)
  - Boker-Dick and Company (Box Box 16)
  - Booth-Ferris Foundation (Box Box 16)
  - Robert Bosch Corporation (Box Box 16)
  - Bowl America Inc. (Box Box 16)
  - Bradlees Department Stores (Box Box 16)
  - Lynale and Harry Bradley Foundation (Box Box 16)
  - Braniff (Box Box 16)
  - Briggs and Straton Corp. (Box Box 16)
  - BWIA International foundation (Box Box 16)
  - The Brown Foundation Inc. (Box Box 16)
  - Brown Mechanical Inc. (Box Box 16)
  - Browning-Ferris Inc. (Box Box 17)
  - The Brunswick Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Buck Trust (Box Box 17)
  - Burger King (Box Box 17)
  - Burlington Industries Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Burlington Northern (Box Box 17)
  - Businessland Inc. (Box Box 17)
  - The Bydale Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Boston Properties (Box Box 17)
  - Boston Properties (Box Box 17)
  - CACI Inc. (Box Box 17)
  - Cambridge International (Box Box 17)
  - The Cameron Baird Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Camp Foundation, VA (Box Box 17)
  - capital Centre (Box Box 17)
  - Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust (Box Box 17)
  - Chanel Inc. (Box Box 17)
  - Change for Good 1987-1988 (Box Box 17)
  - Champion International Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Chemical Bank (Box Box 17)
  - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation (Box Box 17)
  - Cointreau (Box Box 17)
  - Columbia First Federal Savings and Loan (Box Box 17)
  - Columbia Pictures (Box Box 17)
  - Combustioneer (Box Box 17)
  - Communication Through Art (Box Box 17)
  - The Community Resources Institute (Box Box 17)
  - Commonwealth Land Title Insurance Co. (Box Box 17)
  - Congressional Wives Club (Box Box 17)
  - Cornelius-Calabrese Associates, LTD. (Box Box 17)
  - Arena Stage Associates (Box Box 17)
  - Covington and Burling Foundation (Box Box 18)
  - Crown Zellerbach Foundation (Box Box 18)
  - The Trammell Crow Company (Box Box 18)
  - Trammell Crow Company (Box Box 18)
  - Stone, Richard (Box Box 18)
  - O'Neil, Paul (Box Box 18)
  - Olmer, Lionel (Box Box 18)
  - Stoessel, Walter John, Sr. (Box Box 18)
  - Stweart, Patter (Box Box 18)
  - Curry Foundation (Box Box 18)
  - Crum and Foster Foundation (Box Box 18)
  - Melrod, Leonard (Box Box 18)
  - Ourisman, John (Box Box 18)
  - O'Neill, Thomas P. Jr. (Box Box 18)
  - O'Neil, Paul (Box Box 18)
  - Muralock, David (Box Box 18)
  - Ochsman, Ralph (Box Box 18)
  - Munn, David W. (Box Box 18)
  - Moore, Arthur Cotton (Box Box 18)
  - Quinn, Jack (Box Box 18)
  - Preston, Jeanne Clark (Box Box 18)
  - Preston, Barbara and John (Box Box 18)
  - Phipps, Ogden (Box Box 18)
  - Sandground, Mark (Box Box 18)
  - Schwartz, Stewart (Box Box 18)
  - Schattner, Dr. Robert (Box Box 18)
  - Rolanali, Frederick and Mary (Box Box 18)
  - Reynolds, Nancy Susan (Box Box 18)
  - Shosteck, Herschel (Box Box 18)
  - Silvert, Paula Robin (Box Box 18)
  - Small, Albert (Box Box 18)
  - Taylor, Charles (Box Box 18)
  - Wilson, Kendall W. (Box Box 18)
  - Young, William (Box Box 18)
  - Wilkes, Charles Cafrity (Box Box 18)
  - Slandig, Helen Ver (Box Box 18)
  - Taubman, Alfred (Box Box 18)
  - Tarlow, Sherwood (Box Box 18)
  - Stoppard, Tom (Box Box 18)
  - expenditures tables: actual 1977-1978, budgeted 1978-1979 (Box Box 19)
  - budgets estimated and actual 1971-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Business Committee for the Arts (Box Box 19)
  - Cabaret survey by Guthrie (Box Box 19)
  - Packaging Brokerage Business (Box Box 19)
  - production budget 1968-1969 (Box Box 19)
  - production budget, 1969-1970 (Box Box 19)
  - Bresler and Reiner (S.W. Construction) (Box Box 19)
  - general correspondence 1 of 4 (Box Box 19)
  - general correspondence 2 of 4 (Box Box 19)
  - general correspondence 3 of 4 (Box Box 19)
  - general correspondence (Box Box 19)
  - Donor Correspondence (Box Box 20)
  - board of trustees and intro to living stage (Box Box 20)
  - Special Events (Box Box 20)
  - Donor Correspondence (Box Box 20)
  - Donor correspondence and fund raising info (Box Box 20)
  - Donor correspondences and fund raising (Box Box 20)
  - stock certificates and deposit books circa 1956 (Box Box 21)
    Large box containing two 12 column books of stock/gift/donation information. Box also contains loose leaf stock certificates circa 1956, and stock books.
  - NEA grants 1980-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - NEH - Arena Stage History grant (Box Box 22)
  - NEA - Director and Fellowship grant (Box Box 22)
  - NEA - Opera/Musical Theater grant "Rosewater" 1980-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - NEA - Challenge grant application, 1978-1979 (Box Box 22)
  - D.C. Commission for the Arts and Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - The Shubert foundation grant, 1980-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - the Shubert Foundation grant 1980-1981 (Box Box 22)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation grant,1979-1980 (Box Box 22)
  - COMSAT donation, 1980 (Box Box 22)
  - the Cafritz foundation donation, 1981 (Box Box 22)
  - Exxon Corp. grant, 1981-1982 (Box Box 22)
  - Public Welfare foundation donation, 1981 (Box Box 22)
  - Ford Foundation Report (Box Box 22)
  - 1980-1981 potential funding sources (Box Box 22)
  - "Uncle Vanya" production information, 1 of 2 (Box Box 22)
  - "Uncle Vanya" production information, 2 of 2 (Box Box 22)
  - "Uncle Vanya", program proofs (Box Box 22)
  - "Uncle Vanya" Zelda Fichlander notes (Box Box 22)
  - "Vior Dire" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "The Waiting Room" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "The Way of the World" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "What the Butler Saw" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "A Wonderful Life" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "Yerma" production information (Box Box 22)
  - "You Can't Take it With You" production information (Box Box 22)
  - NEA - Living Stage grant application, 1977- 1978 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - Living Stage Expansion Arts grant, 1977-1978 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - Living Stage Expansion proposal 1978-1979 (Box Box 23)
  - Ford Foundation grant, 1978-1979 (Box Box 23)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts grant, 1977-1978 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA Audit 1973 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA grant application 1975-1976 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA grant applications 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - Challenge grant application 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - grant request 1977-1978 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA Directing Intern grant, Gary Pearle 1978-1979 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - Living Stage grants 1978-1979 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA research information, 1979 (Box Box 23)
  - NEH - National Capital Arts and Cultural Affairs 1985-1986 (Box Box 23)
  - NEH - National Capital Arts and Cultural Affairs 1985-1986 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - grant proposal material (Box Box 23)
  - NEH grants 1985-1987 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - grant requests 1987-1988 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - lists 1987-1988 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - lists 1987-1988 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - lists 1987-1988 (Box Box 23)
  - Ford Foundation grants 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Ford Foundation grants 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Ford Foundation, new plat grant 1977-1978 (Box Box 23)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1974-1976 (Box Box 23)
  - grant application forms (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - Living Stage grants 1967-1968 (Box Box 24)
  - 1968-1969 grant allocation (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage grants other than DC Schools (Box Box 24)
  - misc. Living Stage Information (Box Box 24)
  - Health Education and Welfare grant for "The Cage" (Box Box 24)
  - National Foundation of the Arts and Humanities grant for "Great White Hope" (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box Box 24)
  - Grants for Inner City School program, 1969 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - Living Stage grant, 1970 (Box Box 23)
  - NEA - Grant Requests 1969-1970 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - grant requests 1969-1971 (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage, workshops and special contracts 1970-1971 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA- Living Stage grant applications 1970-1971 (Box Box 24)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts grant request, summer workshop (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage Workshops 1971-1972 (Box Box 24)
  - Rockefeller grant 1971-1972 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA Living Stage grant 1971-1972 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - funding for "Dream Engine" 1971-1972 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA grants 1971-1972 (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage financial information, 1972-1973 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA grant request 1972-1973 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - Living Stage grants requests 1972-1973 (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage and B.U. 1972-1973 (Box Box 24)
  - Living Stage financial information 1973-1974 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - Living Stage request 1973-1974 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA grant requests gen. 1973-1974 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA matching grant 1974-1975 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - Visual Arts Grant 1973-1974 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA grants 1974-1975 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA grants 1974-1975 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA - applications 1978-1979 (Box Box 24)
  - NEA application 1978-1978 (Box Box 24)
  - Ford Foundation building grant (Box Box 25)
  - Misc. Foundation grants for construction of Arena II (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation playwright grants (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation actors salaries grant (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation - Travel Grant Request (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation - Production Intern Grant (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation - correspondence (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation playwrights grant 1970-1971 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation grants 1971-1972 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford FOundation playwright grants (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation Playwright grants 1972-1973 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation grant requests 1972-1973 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation - cash reserve 1973 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation report 1978-1979 (Box Box 25)
  - Ford Foundation playwrights 1978-1979 (Box Box 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - training program grant (Box Box 25)
  - Rockefeller grant "Dream Engine" 1971-1972 (Box Box 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation grant requests 1972-1973 (Box Box 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation grants 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - Richard Nelson - Rockefeller grant information (Box Box 25)
  - Cafritz "fifties" grant 1972-1973 (Box Box 25)
  - Cafritz Foundation grants 1972-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Cafritz Foundation grant request 1978-1979 (Box Box 25)
  - Shubet Foundation grants 1972-1978 (Box Box 25)
  - Shubert grant financial information 1976-1978 (Box Box 25)
  - Mellon Foundation grant 1972-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Meyer Foundation grants 1972-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Exxon company donation (Box Box 25)
  - Strong Foundation grant 1974-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Redskins Foundation 1975-1979 (Box Box 25)
  - Billy Rose Foundation 1978-1979 (Box Box 25)
  - Strong Foundation - Living Stage grant 1973-1974 (Box Box 25)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, Living Stage grant 1973-1974 (Box Box 25)
  - NEA, living Stage grant 1974-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Cafritz Foundation requests for Living Stage 1974-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - Strong Foundation application, living Stage 1974-1975 (Box Box 25)
  - NEA Request 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - NEA requests, Living Stage 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - NEA - Expansion Arts grant 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - NEA Living Stage 1975-1976 (Box Box 25)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts and Humanities 1975-1976 (Box Box 25)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - Kreeger Theater land Purchase (Box Box 26)
  - Richard Mohler land donation (Box Box 26)
  - "Closer than Ever" 1990-1991 Royalties (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Cerceau (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: From the Missisippie Delta (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Born Guilty (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Pygmalion (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Before it Hits Home (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: My Children! My Africa! (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Two Gentlemen of Verona (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: She Stoops to Conquer (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: The Seagull (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: On the Way Home (Box Box 26)
  - Royalties: Banjo Dancing (Box Box 26)